Everyone relax. Today's demo is just about confidence.
If we sound certain enough, nobody will ask why the dashboard is still blank.
Wait, you told investors the onboarding flow was already live?
Technically it's live. It just fails for every real customer.
That is not what the deck says.
The deck says what the future wants to hear.
You cannot call imagination a roadmap in front of the board.
I can if the board only looks up when the revenue chart turns red.
So the product has never actually passed a full production test?
Passed? No. Survived? Briefly.
And you're still opening with the line "the system is stable"?
I'm opening with "our momentum is undeniable."
That's not an update. That's a confession with branding.
Fine. What's the truth you want me to say?
That we sold the dream before we built the floor.
And if they walk?
Then at least the lie stops getting payroll.
Okay. No slogans. No fog. We tell them exactly where the product breaks.